<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SAFENEST</string>
    <string name="label">HEALTHY MOMS, STRONG BABIES</string>
    <string name="select_language_hint">Language</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Please enter your name so that we know how to contact you.</string>
    <string name="label_gestational">You need to calculate the gestational age and estimated due date
    for the application to work correctly.</string>
    <string name="enter_first">Enter the first day of your last period.</string>
    <string name="estimated_dueDate">If you know the Estimated Due Date, you may enter it below:</string>

    <string name="sixweek">Congratulations on reaching this milestone!
        You might be experiencing common symptoms like implantation bleeding (light spotting), fatigue, breast tenderness,
        and the onset of nausea and vomiting (morning sickness).</string>
    <string name="fs3">Cook food thoroughly, especially eggs and foods made with eggs, meat, poultry and seafood.</string>
    <string name="fs5">Unpasteurized milk, juice and soft cheeses such as feta, bleu cheese, brie and queso blanco. Soft cheeses made from pasteurized milk are fine.</string>
    <string name="fs7">Swordfish, tilefish, king mackerel and shark, due to high mercury content.</string>
    <string name="wholegrains">Choose whole grains, such as whole wheat bread or pasta, brown rice, quinoa or oats and other\t healthy starches   like beans, lentils, sweet potatoes or acorn squash. Limit     white bread, white rice and fried potatoes</string>
    <string name="protein">Choose\t protein\t sources\t such\t as\t poultry,\t beans,\t nuts,\t low mercury seafood, eggs, tofu or low-fat cheese. Limit red meat and avoid cold cuts and other processed meats.</string>
    <string name="nonstarchy">Choose\t large\t portions\t of\t a\t variety\t of non-starchy vegetables,\t such\t as\t leafy greens,\t broccoli,\t\tcarrots, peppers or cabbage</string>
    <string name="bs1"> Choose a variety of whole fruits. Limit juice and dried fruits. Fruit is great for snacks and dessert, too."</string>
    <string name="bs2">"Choose 2 to 3 servings of nonfat or 1% milk or yogurt (cow, soy or almond). A serving is 8 oz. Choose yogurt with less than 15 g of sugar per serving."</string>
    <string name="bs3">Drink mainly water, decaf tea or decaf coffee and avoid sugary beverages.</string>
    <string name="bs4">Aim for at least 30 minutes of walking or another physical activity each day.</string>
    <string name="bs5">Choose small amounts of healthy oils (olive and canola) for cooking or to flavor foods. Nuts, seeds and avocados contain healthy fats </string>
    <string name="week2">
        At the start of this week, you ovulate. Your egg is fertilized 12 to
        24 hours later if a sperm penetrates it. Over the next several
        days, the fertilized egg will start dividing into multiple cells as it
        travels down the fallopian tube, enters your uterus, and starts to
        burrow into the uterine lining. \n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 2nd week: \n\n
        Ovulation:\n
        \t\t• Egg development: An egg starts maturing in one of your \n\t\t\t ovaries, inside a fluid-filled sac called a follicle.
        \n\t\t• Hormonal changes: Levels of estrogen and \n\t\t\t follicle-stimulating
        hormone (FSH) increase, stimulating the \n\t\t\t egg\'s growth.
        \n\t\t• Ovulation event: Around day 14 (can vary depending on your
        \n\t\t\t cycle), the mature egg ruptures from the follicle and is
        \n\t\t\t released into the fallopian tube, ready for fertilization.

        \n\nPossible symptoms you might experience:\n
       \t\t• Mittelschmerz: A mild pain or twinge in your lower abdomen \n\t\t\t on one side, indicating ovulation.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus changes: Mucus becomes thinner and \n\t\t\t clearer,
        more receptive to sperm.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Consult with a healthcare professional if you have any
        \n\t\t\t questions or concerns about your menstrual cycle or
        \n\t\t\t conception.
       \n\t\t• Accurate pregnancy dating starts from the first day of your
        \n\t\t\t last menstrual period, not week 2.
    </string>

    <string name="week3">
        Now nestled in the nutrient-rich lining of your uterus is a
        microscopic ball of hundreds of rapidly multiplying cells that will
        develop into your baby. This ball of cells, called a blastocyst, has
        begun to produce the pregnancy hormone hCG, which tells your
        ovaries to stop releasing eggs\n\nHere\'s what happens during the 3rd week: \n
        \n\t\t• Implantation: This is the star of the show! By week 3, the
        \n\t\t\t fertilized egg, now called a blastocyst, has traveled down
        \n\t\t\t your fallopian tube and burrows itself into the lining of your
        \n\t\t\t uterus. This process usually takes about 6-10 days after
        \n\t\t\t ovulation

        \n\t\t• Early cell differentiation: The blastocyst starts to \n\t\t\t differentiate
        into two groups of cells: the inner cell mass \n\t\t\t (which will
        eventually become your baby) and the outer layer \n\t\t\t (which will
        form the placenta and other supportive \n\t\t\t structures).

        \n\t\t• Placenta formation: The outer layer of the blastocyst begins
        \n\t\t\t to develop into the placenta, a vital organ that will nourish
        \n\t\t\t your baby and remove waste products throughout \n\t\t\t pregnancy.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Implantation bleeding: Some women experience light
        \n\t\t\t spotting or bleeding around the time of implantation, which
        \n\t\t\t can be mistaken for a period. This is usually nothing to worry
        \n\t\t\t about, but if you have any concerns, consult your doctor.

        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness: Rising hormone levels can make your
        \n\t\t\t breasts feel swollen and tender.

        \n\t\t• Fatigue: You might feel more tired than usual due to
        \n\t\t\t hormonal changes and the body\'s increased energy \n\t\t\t demands.

        \n\t\t• Food cravings or aversions: Some women experience \n\t\t\t changes
        in their sense of taste and smell, leading to cravings \n\t\t\t for
        certain foods or aversions to others.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: It\'s important to remember that not everyone
        \n\t\t\t experiences pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and \n\t\t\t some
        women might not feel anything at all in the early \n\t\t\t weeks.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Prenatal vitamin: Start taking a prenatal vitamin that \n\t\t\t contains
        folic acid and other essential nutrients to support \n\t\t\t your baby\'s development.
        \n\t\t•Healthy lifestyle: Focus on eating a balanced diet, getting
        \n\t\t\t regular exercise, and staying hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Doctor\'s visit: Schedule a prenatal appointment with your
        \n\t\t\t doctor to discuss your pregnancy and any concerns you \n\t\t\t have.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Weight gain: You likely won\'t experience any significant \n\t\t\t weight gain in the third week.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: If you\'ve been tracking your basal \n\t\t\t body temperature, it should remain elevated after ovulation.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: Your cervical mucus might become thicker \n\t\t\t and creamier as your body prepares for implantation.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and the experiences mentioned \n\t\t\t above are just general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• If you have any concerns or questions, don\'t hesitate to \n\t\t\t talk to your doctor
    </string>

    <string name="week4">
        Your ball of cells is now officially an embryo.
        You\'re now about 4 weeks from the beginning of your last period.
        It\'s around this time– when your next period would normally be due –
        that you might be able to get a positive result on a home pregnancy test\n
        \nYour baby is the size of a poppy seed\n\nHere\'s what happens during the 4th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Rapid cell division: The inner cell mass from the blastocyst
        \n\t\t\t apidly divides and forms three distinct layers: the ectoderm
        \n\t\t\t (forms skin, hair, and nervous system), endoderm (forms
        \n\t\t\t digestive and respiratory systems), and mesoderm (forms
        \n\t\t\t muscles, bones, blood vessels, and other organs).
        \n\t\t• Primitive streak formation: A line of cells appears within the
        \n\t\t\t inner cell mass, called the primitive streak, which will
        \n\t\t\t eventually develop into the baby\'s nervous system.

        \n\t\t• Yolk sac development: A small sac outside the embryo, called
        \n\t\t\t the yolk sac, provides early nourishment until the placenta
        \n\t\t\t takes over.

        \n\t\t• Amniotic sac development: A fluid-filled sac forms around \n\t\t\t the
        embryo, creating a protective environment.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Implantation bleeding: Some women may still experience \n\t\t\tlight
        spotting or bleeding.
        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may continue to feel
        \n\t\t\t swollen and tender, and nipples may become darker.
        \n\t\t• Fatigue: Feeling unusually tired is common due to hormonal
        \n\t\t\t changes and increased energy demands.
        \n\t\t• Nausea and vomiting: Morning sickness (which can occur at
        \n\t\t\t any time of day) may start affecting some women.
        \n\t\t• Food cravings or aversions: Changes in taste and smell can
        \n\t\t\t lead to specific cravings or aversions.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
        \n\t\t\t feel anything yet.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintain taking your prenatal
        \n\t\t\t vitamin for essential nutrients.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, regular exercise,
        \n\t\t\t and proper hydration.
        \n\t\t•Schedule prenatal appointment: If you haven\'t already, book
        \n\t\t\t a prenatal appointment with your doctor for early pregnancy
        \n\t\t\t check-ups and guidance.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Weight gain: Minimal weight gain, if any, is expected at this
        \n\t\t\t stage.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Likely remains elevated if you\'ve
        \n\t\t\t been tracking it.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thicker and stickier as your \n\t\t\t body
        prepares for continued pregnancy.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions.





    </string>

    <string name="week5">
        \n Your baby resembles a tadpole more than a human, but is
        \n growing fast. The circulatory system is beginning to form, and
        \n cells in the tiny
        "heart"
        will start to flicker this week.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a sesame seed.\n\n

        Here\'s what happens during the 5th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Embryo growth: The embryo grows rapidly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a sesame seed.
        \n\t\t• Neural tube formation: The neural tube forms, which will
         \n\t\t\t eventually become the brain and spinal cord.
        \n\t\t• Heart development: The tiny heart starts beating, although
        \n\t\t\t it\'s still a simple tube structure.
        \n\t\t• Blood vessel development: The first blood vessels form,
        \n\t\t\t connecting the embryo to the developing placenta.
        \n\t\t• Placenta development: The placenta continues to grow and
        \n\t\t\t take over nourishing the embryo.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: Nausea and vomiting are common,
        \n\t\t\t although not everyone experiences them.
        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may continue to feel
        \n\t\t\t swollen and tender, and nipples may darken.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: You might need to urinate more often
        \n\t\t\t due to increased blood volume and pressure on the bladder.
        \n\t\t• Food cravings or aversions: Changes in taste and smell can
        \n\t\t\t  lead to specific preferences or dislikes.
        \n\t\t• Bloating: Increased progesterone levels can cause bloating.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Not everyone experiences pregnancy
        \n\t\t\t symptoms, and some might not feel anything yet.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintain taking your prenatal
        \n\t\t\t vitamin for essential nutrients.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointment: If you haven\'t already, book
        \n\t\t\t a prenatal appointment with your doctor for early
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy check-ups and guidance.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, regular exercise,
        \n\t\t\t and proper hydration.\n\n


        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Weight gain: Minimal weight gain, if any, is expected at this
        \n\t\t\t stage.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature:  No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy after ovulation.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thicker and stickier to support \n\t\t\t pregnancy.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions.
    </string>


    <string name="week6">
        Your baby\'s nose, mouth and ears are starting to take shape, and
        their intestines and brain are beginning to develop.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a lentil.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 6th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Rapid growth: The embryo, now called a fetus, nearly
        \n\t\t\tdoubles in size, reaching about the size of a lentil.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Tiny bumps appear where the eyes, nose,
        \n\t\t\tand ears will eventually form.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Tiny buds form, which will develop into
        \n\t\t\tarms and legs.
        \n\t\t• Internal organ development: The heart continues to beat, \n\t\t\tand
        the beginnings of the brain, lungs, and digestive system
        \n\t\t\tappear.
        \n\t\t• Placenta function: The placenta starts transferring nutrients
        \n\t\t\tand oxygen to the fetus and removing waste products.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: This is still common, and it can affect
        \n\t\t\twomen differently.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
        \n\t\t\tvolume and pressure on the bladder.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Hormonal changes can cause emotional
        \n\t\t\tfluctuations.
        \n\t\t• Bloating: Increased progesterone levels can still cause \n\t\t\tbloating.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Not everyone experiences pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tsymptoms, and some might not feel anything yet.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintain taking your prenatal
        \n\t\t\t vitamin for essential nutrients.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointment: If you haven\'t already, book
        \n\t\t\t a prenatal appointment with your doctor for early
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy check-ups and guidance.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, regular exercise,
        \n\t\t\t(with doctor\'s approval), and proper hydration.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Weight gain: Minimal weight gain, if any, is expected at this
        \n\t\t\t stage.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature:  Not relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy anymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thicker and stickier to support \n\t\t\t pregnancy.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions.

    </string>

    <string name="week7">
        Your baby has doubled in size since last week, but still has a tail,
        which will soon disappear. Little hands and feet that look more
        like paddles are emerging from the developing arms and legs.
        \n\nYour baby is the size of a blueberry.
        \n\nHere\'s what happens during the 7th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth spurt: The fetus grows rapidly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a blueberry.
        \n\t\t• Facial structure: The facial features become more defined,
        \n\t\t\t with eyes forming eyelids and nostrils appearing.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Arm and leg buds become more distinct,
        \n\t\t\t with fingers and toes starting to develop.
        \n\t\t• Organ development: The brain, lungs, digestive system, and
        \n\t\t\t other organs continue to develop and become more \n\t\t\t complex.
        \n\t\t• Nervous system development: The nervous system matures,
        \n\t\t\t allowing for basic movements and reflexes.
        \n\t\t• Circulatory system development: The heart beats strong and
        \n\t\t\t pumps blood throughout the developing body.\n\n
        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: This can continue for some women, though
        \n\t\t\t it might start to improve for others.
        \n\t\t• Fatigue: Tiredness remains common due to hormonal
        \n\t\t\t  changes and increased energy demands.
       \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may continue to feel
        \n\t\t\t swollen and tender, and nipples may become darker and
        \n\t\t\t larger.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite: As your body nourishes the growing\n\t\t\t fetus,
        \n\t\t\t you might feel hungrier more often.
        \n\t\t• Food cravings or aversions: Changes in taste and smell can
        \n\t\t\t  still occur.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
        \n\t\t\t  volume and pressure on the bladder.
        \n\t\t• Bloating: Progesterone levels can still cause bloating.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Hormonal fluctuations can lead to emotional
        \n\t\t\t  ups and downs.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Not everyone experiences pregnancy
        \n\t\t\t symptoms in the same way, and some might not feel \n\t\t\t  anything yet.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: It\'s crucial to keep taking your
        \n\t\t\t prenatal vitamin for essential nutrients.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Attend regular check-ups
        \n\t\t\t with your doctor to monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t development.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Maintain a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider genetic testing: Discuss with your doctor if you
        \n\t\t\t have any concerns or risk factors for genetic conditions and
        \n\t\t\t whether genetic testing is right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Slight weight gain: You might start noticing a subtle increase
        \n\t\t\t in weight as your body nourishes the fetus.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Possible visible changes: Your clothes might start to feel a bit
        \n\t\t\t snugger around your abdomen, but a noticeable baby bump
        \n\t\t\t is unlikely at this stage.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.


    </string>
    <string name="week9">
        Your baby\'s basic anatomy is developing (they even have tiny earlobes now), but there\'s much more to come.
        Their embryonic
        tail has disappeared and they weigh just a fraction of an ounce
        but are about to start gaining weight fast.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a grape.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 9th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The fetus grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a grape.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to become more
        \n\t\t\t detailed, with eyelids opening and closing, and the
        \n\t\t\t beginnings of teeth forming.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed, with
        \n\t\t\t tiny nails visible. Muscles and bones develop further,
        \n\t\t\t allowing for more complex movements.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Internal organs continue to mature rapidly,
        \n\t\t\t with the brain showing significant development and the
        \n\t\t\t digestive system becoming more functional.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals develop more externally, and
        \n\t\t\t in some cases, the baby\'s sex may be discernible through
        \n\t\t\t ultrasound.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: For some women, this may start to improve
        \n\t\t\t or lessen in intensity.
        \n\t\t• Fatigue: While still common, fatigue might decrease as your
        \n\t\t\t body adjusts to hormonal changes.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite and food cravings/aversions: Your body
        \n\t\t\t needs more fuel for growth, leading to increased hunger
        \n\t\t\t and potential changes in taste and smell.
        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may still feel swollen
        \n\t\t\t and tender, but the tenderness typically starts to decrease.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
        \n\t\t\t volume and pressure on the bladder.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Hormonal fluctuations can still cause
        \n\t\t\t emotional ups and downs, but hopefully less intense than
        \n\t\t\t before.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You might start noticing a slight bump
        \n\t\t\t around your lower abdomen, although it\'s not yet a true
        \n\t\t\t baby bump.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
        \n\t\t\t feel anything yet.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintaining your prenatal vitamin
        \n\t\t\t intake is crucial for continued development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\t your doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t progress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t adequately hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor
        \n\t\t\t whether prenatal screening tests like ultrasound or genetic
        \n\t\t\t testing are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a steady increase in
        \n\t\t\t weight as your body nourishes the growing fetus.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Possible visible changes: A slight bump around your lower
        \n\t\t\t abdomen might be noticeable, but a prominent baby bump
        \n\t\t\t  is still not typical.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>
    <string name="week8">
        Your baby has started moving around, though you won\'t feel your
        baby move yet. Nerve cells are branching out, forming primitive
        neural pathways. Breathing tubes now extend from their throat to
        their developing lungs.\n\n

        Your baby is the size of a kidney bean.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 8th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The fetus grows dramatically, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t  the size of a kidney bean.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to become more
        \n\t\t\t  defined, with eyelids closing completely for a short period
        \n\t\t\t  and the nose becoming more prominent.
        \n\t\t•Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed, with
        \n\t\t\t  tiny nails starting to appear.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and bone development: Muscles and bones start to
        \n\t\t\t  develop, allowing for basic movements like flexing and
        \n\t\t\t kicking.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Internal organs continue to mature, with the
        \n\t\t\t  brain showing significant development and the digestive
        \n\t\t\t system becoming more functional
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals begin to develop externally,
        \n\t\t\t although it\'s still too early to determine the baby\'s sex.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: This might start to improve for some
        \n\t\t\t women, while others might continue to experience it.
        \n\t\t• Fatigue: Tiredness remains common due to hormonal
        \n\t\t\t changes and increased energy demands.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite and food cravings/aversions: Your body
       \n\t\t\t needs more fuel for growth, leading to increased hunger
         \n\t\t\t and potential changes in taste and smell.
        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may continue to feel
         \n\t\t\t swollen and tender, with nipples becoming darker and  \n\t\t\t larger.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
         \n\t\t\t volume and pressure on the bladder.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Hormonal fluctuations can still cause
        \n\t\t\t emotional ups and downs.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You might start noticing subtle changes in
         \n\t\t\t your body shape, but a pronounced baby bump is unlikely
         \n\t\t\t yet.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
         \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
         \n\t\t\t feel anything yet.

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintaining your prenatal vitamin
        \n\t\t\t intake is crucial for continued development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\t your doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t progress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t adequately hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor
        \n\t\t\t whether prenatal screening tests like ultrasound or genetic
        \n\t\t\t testing are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Slight weight gain: You might start noticing a subtle increase
        \n\t\t\t in weight as your body nourishes the fetus.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Possible visible changes: Clothes might feel a bit snugger,
        \n\t\t\t but a prominent baby bump is still not typical.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>
    <string name="week10">
        Your embryo has completed the most critical portion of
        development. Their skin is still translucent, but their tiny limbs can
        bend and fine details like nails are starting to form.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a kumquat.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 10th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The fetus grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a kumquat.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to refine, with the
        \n\t\t\t nose becoming more prominent and the lips forming.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed with
        \n\t\t\t tiny fingernails and toenails. Muscles and bones develop
        \n\t\t\tfurther, allowing for more complex movements like kicking
        \n\t\t\tand flexing.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Internal organs continue to mature rapidly,
        \n\t\t\t with the brain showing complex activity and the digestive
        \n\t\t\t system becoming even more functional.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\t baby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\t desired.\n\n
        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: This tends to improve significantly for most
        \n\t\t\t women by this week, although some may still experience
        \n\t\t\t nausea or vomiting occasionally.
        \n\t\t• Increased energy: As your body adjusts to hormonal
        \n\t\t\t changes, you may feel more energetic than in previous
        \n\t\t\tweeks.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite and food cravings/aversions: Your body
        \n\t\t\t still needs more fuel, but cravings may become less intense
       \n\t\t\t or even disappear.
        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may still feel slightly
        \n\t\t\t tender, but the discomfort should be significantly reduced.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
        \n\t\t\t volume and pressure on the bladder, but might become less
        \n\t\t\t frequent than before.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations can still occur, but
        \n\t\t\t hopefully less intense and frequent than earlier weeks.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You might start noticing a more defined
        \n\t\t\t bump around your lower abdomen, marking the beginning
        \n\t\t\t of your visible baby bump.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
        \n\t\t\t feel anything noticeable.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintaining your prenatal vitamin
        \n\t\t\t intake is crucial for continued development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\t your doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t progress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t adequately hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor
        \n\t\t\t whether prenatal screening tests like ultrasound or genetic
        \n\t\t\t testing are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Steady weight gain: You might notice a steady increase in
        \n\t\t\t weight as your body nourishes the growing fetus.
         \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
         \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
       \n\t\t\t  pregnancy, but becoming less so gradually.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: A more defined bump around your lower
        \n\t\t\t abdomen is likely, marking the start of your visible baby bump.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week11">
        Your baby is almost fully formed. They\'re kicking, stretching, and
        even hiccupping as their diaphragm develops, although you can\'t
        feel any activity yet.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a fig.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 11th week:
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The fetus grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a fig.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to refine, with
        \n\t\t\t distinct human characteristics like eyelids, lips, and a tiny
        \n\t\t\t nose becoming more prominent.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed with
        \n\t\t\t tiny fingernails and toenails, and the baby might start
        \n\t\t\t flexing and stretching limbs.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Internal organs continue to mature rapidly,
        \n\t\t\t with the brain showing complex activity, the digestive
        \n\t\t\t system becoming more functional, and the kidneys starting
        \n\t\t\t to produce urine.
        \n\t\t• Skeletal development: Bones become harder and more
        \n\t\t\t developed, allowing for more coordinated movements.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\t baby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\t desired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: This should significantly improve for most
        \n\t\t\t women, although occasional nausea or vomiting might still
        \n\t\t\t occur.
        \n\t\t• Increased energy: You might feel more energetic than in
        \n\t\t\t previous weeks as your body adjusts to hormonal changes.
        \n\t\t\tIncreased appetite and food cravings/aversions: Your body
        \n\t\t\t still needs more fuel, but cravings may become less intense
        \n\t\t\t or even disappear.
        \n\t\t•Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may still feel slightly
        \n\t\t\t tender, but the discomfort should be significantly reduced.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
        \n\t\t\t volume and pressure on the bladder, but might become less
        \n\t\t\t frequent than before.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations can still occur, but
        \n\t\t\t hopefully less intense and frequent than earlier weeks.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more noticeable
        \n\t\t\t and defined, and some women might start experiencing skin
        \n\t\t\t changes like a pregnancy glow.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
        \n\t\t\tfeel anything noticeable.\n \n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintaining your prenatal vitamin
        \n\t\t\t intake is crucial for continued development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\t your doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t progress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t adequately hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor
        \n\t\t\t whether prenatal screening tests like ultrasound or genetic
        \n\t\t\t testing are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Steady weight gain: You might notice a steady increase in
        \n\t\t\t weight as your body nourishes the growing fetus.
         \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
         \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
       \n\t\t\t  pregnancy, but becoming less so gradually.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: A more defined bump around your lower
        \n\t\t\t abdomen is likely, marking the start of your visible baby
        \n\t\t\t bump.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>


    <string name="week12">
        This week your baby\'s reflexes kick in: Their fingers will soon begin
        to open and close, toes will curl, and their mouth will make
        sucking movements.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a lime.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 12th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Entering the second trimester: This week marks the exciting
        \n\t\t\t transition into the second trimester, which is often referred
        \n\t\t\t to as the "honeymoon phase" due to decreased nausea and
        \n\t\t\t increased energy levels for many women.
       \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The fetus grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a lime.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to develop with
        \n\t\t\t distinct characteristics becoming more recognizable,
        \n\t\t\t including eyebrows, eyelids, and a more defined nose.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed with
        \n\t\t\t tiny fingernails and toenails, and the baby might start
        \n\t\t\t grasping, sucking their thumb, and making more
        \n\t\t\t coordinated movements.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Internal organs continue to mature rapidly,
        \n\t\t\t with the brain showing complex activity, the digestive
        \n\t\t\t system absorbing nutrients from swallowed amniotic fluid,
        \n\t\t\t and the kidneys functioning more efficiently.
        \n\t\t• Skeletal development: Bones become stronger and more
        \n\t\t\t developed, allowing for more coordinated movements and
        \n\t\t\t muscle development.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\t baby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\t desired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Reduced morning sickness: For most women, the dreaded
        \n\t\t\t morning sickness should significantly improve or disappear
        \n\t\t\t altogether by this week.
        \n\t\t• Increased energy: You might feel more energetic and vibrant
        \n\t\t\t as hormonal changes stabilize and nausea subsides.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite: Your body needs more fuel for the
        \n\t\t\t growing baby, so you might feel hungrier more often.
        \n\t\t• Food cravings/aversions: While still possible, these
        \n\t\t\t  tendencies
        \n\t\t\t often become less intense or disappear entirely.
        \n\t\t• Reduced breast tenderness: The discomfort in your breasts
        \n\t\t\t should be significantly reduced by now.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: You might still need to urinate more often
        \n\t\t\t due to increased blood volume and pressure on the bladder,
        \n\t\t\t but less frequently than earlier weeks.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still occur, but
        \n\t\t\t hopefully less intense and frequent than in the first
        \n\t\t\t trimester.
        \n\t\t•Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more noticeable
        \n\t\t\t and defined, and some women might start experiencing skin
        \n\t\t\t changes like a"pregnancy glow" or linea nigra (a dark line
        \n\t\t\t down the abdomen).
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
        \n\t\t\t feel anything noticeable.\n\n

         Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintaining your prenatal vitamin
        \n\t\t\t intake is crucial for continued development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\t your doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t progress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t adequately hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor
        \n\t\t\t whether prenatal screening tests like ultrasound or genetic
        \n\t\t\t testing are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Steady weight gain: You might notice a steady increase in
        \n\t\t\t weight as your body nourishes the growing fetus.
         \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
         \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
       \n\t\t\t  pregnancy, but becoming less so gradually.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: A more defined bump around your lower
        \n\t\t\t abdomen is likely, marking the start of your visible baby
        \n\t\t\t bump.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>
    <string name="week13">This is the last week of your first trimester. Your baby\'s tiny fingers
        now have fingerprints, and their veins and organs are clearly
        visible through their skin. If you\'re having a girl, her ovaries
        contain more than 2 million eggs.
        \n\nYour baby is the size of a pea pod.
        \n\nHere\'s what happens during the 13th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Entering the "honeymoon phase": You\'re officially in the
        \n\t\t\tsecond trimester, often considered a more comfortable
        \n\t\t\tperiod with reduced nausea and increased energy for many
        \n\t\t\twomen.
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The baby grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\tthe size of a pea pod.
         \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features refine further, with distinct
        \n\t\t\texpressions visible on ultrasound.
         \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes become more
        \n\t\t\tcoordinated, and the baby might engage in grasping,
        \n\t\t\tsucking, and kicking movements.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature rapidly, with the
         \n\t\t\tbrain showing even more complex activity, the digestive
         \n\t\t\tsystem absorbing nutrients from amniotic fluid, and the
         \n\t\t\tkidneys functioning more efficiently.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop, allowing
         \n\t\t\tfor more coordinated movements, and bones strengthen
         \n\t\t\tfurther.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
         \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
         \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
         \n\t\t• Reduced or absent morning sickness: Nausea and vomiting
        \n\t\t\tshould significantly improve or disappear for most women by
        \n\t\t\tthis point.
         \n\t\t• Increased energy: You might feel more energetic and vibrant
        \n\t\t\tdue to hormonal changes stabilizing.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite: Your body needs more fuel, so you might
        \n\t\t\tfeel hungrier more often.
         \n\t\t•  Food cravings/aversions: These might still occur but are
        \n\t\t\toften less intense or completely gone.
         \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
       \n\t\t\tand some women experience skin changes like a \'pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tglow\ or linear nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
         \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Steady weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
 </string>

    <string name="week14">
        Your baby\'s brain impulses have begun to fire and they\'re using
        their facial muscles. Their kidneys are working now, too. If you
        have an ultrasound, you may even see them sucking their thumb.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a lemon.\n\n

        Here\'s what happens during the 14th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Embracing the second trimester: You
        \'re fully in the second
        \n\t\t\ttrimester, often described as a period of increased energy
        \n\t\t\tand reduced nausea for many women.
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The baby grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\tthe size of a lemon.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to refine, with
        \n\t\t\tdistinct expressions becoming even more visible on
        \n\t\t\tultrasound.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes become even more
        \n\t\t\tcoordinated, and the baby might be actively grasping,
        \n\t\t\tsucking, and kicking.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature rapidly, with the
        \n\t\t\tbrain showing even more complex activity, the digestive
        \n\t\t\tsystem absorbing more nutrients from amniotic fluid, and the
        \n\t\t\tkidneys functioning even more efficiently
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for even more coordinated movements, and bones
        \n\t\t\tcontinue to strengthen.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:\n
        \n\t\t• Decreased fatigue: You might feel more energetic and
        \n\t\t\tvibrant as your body adjusts to hormonal changes.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite: Your body needs more fuel for the
        \n\t\t\tgrowing baby, so you might feel hungrier more often.
        \n\t\t• Food cravings/aversions: These might still occur but are
        \n\t\t\toften less intense or completely gone.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women experience skin changes like a
        \'pregnancy \n\t\t\tglow\' or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n
        Expectations for your body:\n
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a steady increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week15">
        Your baby\'s eyelids are still fused shut, but they can sense light.
        If you shine a flashlight on your tummy, they\'ll move away from the
        beam. Ultrasounds done this week may reveal your baby\'s sex.
        \n\nYour baby is the size of an apple.
        \n\nHere\'s what happens during the 15th week:
        \n\t\t• Embracing the second trimester: You
        \'re fully in the second
        \n\t\t\ttrimester, often described as a period of increased energy
        \n\t\t\tand reduced nausea for many women.
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The baby grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\tthe size of a apple.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features become even more
        \n\t\t\tdeveloped and distinct, with eyebrows and eyelashes visible
        \n\t\t\ton ultrasound.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes become even more
        \n\t\t\tcoordinated, and the baby might be actively grasping,
        \n\t\t\tsucking, and kicking.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue their rapid maturation, with
        \n\t\t\tthe brain showing even more complex activity, the digestive
       \n\t\t\tsystem absorbing more nutrients from amniotic fluid, and the
        \n\t\t\tkidneys functioning even more efficiently
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for even more coordinated movements, and bones
        \n\t\t\tcontinue to strengthen.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy: You might feel more energetic and vibrant
        \n\t\t\tas your body adjusts to hormonal changes.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite: Your body needs more fuel for the
        \n\t\t\tgrowing baby, so you might feel hungrier more often.
        \n\t\t• Reduced nausea/morning sickness: This should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly reduced or absent for most women by now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women experience skin changes like a
        \'pregnancy \n\t\t\tglow\' or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
        \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and some
        \n\t\t\twomen might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="week16">
        The patterning on your baby\'s scalp has begun, though their hair isn\'t visible yet. Their legs are more developed, their head is more
        upright, and their ears are close to their final position.
        \n\nYour baby is the size of an avocado.
        \n\nHere\'s what happens during the 16th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Second trimester continues: You\'re firmly in the second
        \n\t\t\ttrimester, often considered the \"honeymoon phase\" due
        \n\t\t\tto increased energy and reduced nausea for many women.
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The baby grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\tthe size of an avocado.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features become even more distinct,
        \n\t\t\tand the baby might be starting to form facial expressions.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed with
        \n\t\t\ttiny fingernails and toenails, and the baby might be actively
        \n\t\t\tgrasping, sucking, kicking, and even hiccupping.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue their rapid maturation, with
        \n\t\t\tthe brain showing even more complex activity, the digestive
        \n\t\t\tsystem absorbing more nutrients from amniotic fluid, and the
       \n\t\t\tkidneys functioning even more efficiently
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements, and bones
        \n\t\t\tcontinue to strengthen.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

         Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy: You might feel more energetic and vibrant
        \n\t\t\tas your body adjusts to hormonal changes.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite: Your body needs more fuel for the
        \n\t\t\tgrowing baby, so you might feel hungrier more often.
        \n\t\t• Reduced nausea/morning sickness: This should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly reduced or absent for most women by now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women experience skin changes like a
        \'pregnancy \n\t\t\tglow\' or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
        \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Forgetfulness: You might experience increased forgetfulness
        \n\t\t\tor \"pregnancy brain\" due to hormonal changes.
        \n\t\t• symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and some
        \n\t\t\twomen might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

         Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>

    <string name="week17">
        Your baby can move their joints, and their skeleton – formerly soft
        cartilage – is now hardening to bone. The umbilical cord is
        growing stronger and thicker.\n\n

        Your baby is the size of a turnip.
        \n\nHere\'s what happens during the 17th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The baby continues to grow significantly,
        \n\t\t\treaching about the size of a turnip (around 12cm from head
        \n\t\t\tto bottom).
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features refine further, with eyebrows
        \n\t\t\tand eyelashes becoming more visible. The baby might even
        \n\t\t\tstart opening and closing their eyes!
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes are well-defined with
        \n\t\t\ttiny fingernails and toenails. Muscles and bones continue to
        \n\t\t\tdevelop, allowing for more coordinated movements like
       \n\t\t\tkicking and flexing.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature rapidly. The brain
        \n\t\t\tshows even more complex activity, the digestive system
        \n\t\t\tbecomes more functional, and the kidneys start producing \n\t\t\turine.
        \n\t\t• Skeletal development: Bones become harder and more
        \n\t\t\tdeveloped, enabling more coordinated movements.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Decreased fatigue: Most women experience increased
        \n\t\t\tenergy levels in the second trimester, leaving them feeling
        \n\t\t\tless tired than earlier weeks.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite: As the baby grows, your body needs
        \n\t\t\tmorefuel, so you might feel hungrier more often.
       \n\t\t• Food cravings/aversions: These might still occur, but typically
        \n\t\t\tbecome less intense or disappear entirely.
        \n\t\t• Reduced nausea: Morning sickness should be significantly
        \n\t\t\timproved or absent for most women by now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more noticeable,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t\"pregnancy glow\" or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might continue due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less
        \n\t\t\tfrequently than before.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience any noticeable
        \n\t\t\tsymptoms.\n\n

           Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n



        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Steady weight gain: You might notice a steady increase in
        \n\t\t\t weight as your body nourishes the growing fetus.
         \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week18">
        Your baby is flexing their arms and legs, and you may be able to
        feel those movements. Internally, a protective coating of myelin is
        forming around their nerves.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a bell pepper.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 18th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Entering the heart of the second trimester: You\'re enjoying
        \n\t\t\tthe often-mentioned \"honeymoon phase
        \"with increased
        \n\t\t\tenergy and reduced nausea for many women.
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The baby reaches about the size of a bell
        \n\t\t\tpepper (around 14.2cm long from head to bottom).
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features become more distinct, with
        \n\t\t\trecognizable eyes, nose, and lips.
        \n\t\t• Movement: You might start feeling your baby move around
        \n\t\t\tthis week, although some women don\'t feel it until later.
        \n\t\t\tThese early movements are often described as flutters,
        \n\t\t\t bubbles, or kicks.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue their rapid maturation, with
        \n\t\t\tthe brain showing even more complex activity, the digestive
        \n\t\t\tsystem becoming more active, and the kidneys functioning
        \n\t\t\tmore efficiently.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements, and bones
        \n\t\t\tcontinue to strengthen.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

         Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy: You might feel more energetic and vibrant
        \n\t\t\tas your body adjusts to hormonal changes.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite: Your body needs more fuel for the
        \n\t\t\tgrowing baby, so you might feel hungrier more often.
         \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: This should be significantly
        \n\t\t\timproved or disappeared entirely for most women by now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women experience skin changes like a
        \'pregnancy \n\t\t\tglow\' or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
        \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Forgetfulness: You might experience increased forgetfulness
        \n\t\t\tor \"pregnancy brain\" due to hormonal changes.
        \n\t\t• symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and some
        \n\t\t\twomen might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>
    <string name="week19">
        Your baby\'s senses – smell, vision, touch, taste and hearing – are
        developing and they may be able to hear your voice. Talk, sing or
        read out loud to them, if you feel like it.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of an heirloom tomato.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 19th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: Your baby continues to grow significantly,
        \n\t\t\treaching about the size of an heirloom tomato (around
        \n\t\t\t15.2cm long from head to bottom).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Most women start feeling their baby move
        \n\t\t\taround this week, although some might not feel it until later.
        \n\t\t\tThese movements become more frequent and distinct over \n\t\t\ttime.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: The brain develops rapidly, with
        \n\t\t\tincreased activity and complex connections forming.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature rapidly. The
        \n\t\t\tlungs start practicing breathing motions, and the digestive
        \n\t\t\tsystem absorbs nutrients from amniotic fluid.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements, and bones
        \n\t\t\tcontinue to strengthen
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women by
        \n\t\t\tnow.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week20">
        Your baby can swallow now and their digestive system is
        producing meconium, the dark, sticky goo that they
        \'ll pass in their first poop – either in their diaper or in the womb during delivery.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a banana.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 20th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a banana
        \n\t\t\t(around 15.2cm long from head to bottom).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Most women start feeling their baby move 
        \n\t\t\taround this week, though some might not feel it until later. 
        \n\t\t\tThese movements become more frequent and distinct over \n\t\t\ttime.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly with
        \n\t\t\tincreased activity and complex connections forming.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature rapidly. Lungs
        \n\t\t\tpractice breathing motions, and the digestive system 
        \n\t\t\tabsorbs nutrients from amniotic fluid.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements. Bones continue 
        \n\t\t\tto strengthen
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
       \n\t\t\tdesired.

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women by
        \n\t\t\tnow.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week21">
        Your baby \'s movements have gone from flutters to full-on kicks
        and jabs against the walls of your womb. You may start to notice
        patterns as you become more familiar with their activity.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a carrot.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 21st week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a carrot
        \n\t\t\t(around 26.7cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Most women feel their baby move regularly by
        \n\t\t\tnow, and these movements become more distinct and
        \n\t\t\tfrequent.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly with
        \n\t\t\tincreased activity and complex connections forming.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature rapidly. Kidneys
        \n\t\t\tfunction more efficiently, and the digestive system absorbs
        \n\t\t\tmore nutrients from amniotic fluid.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements. Bones continue
        \n\t\t\tto strengthen, and hair and eyebrows become visible on
        \n\t\t\tultrasound.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women by
        \n\t\t\tnow.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="week22">
        Your baby now looks almost like a miniature newborn. Features
        such as lips and eyebrows are more distinct, but the pigment that
        will color their eyes isn\'t present yet.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a spaghetti squash.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 22nd week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a
        \n\t\t\tspaghetti squash (around 27.8cm from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Most women feel their baby move regularly by
        \n\t\t\tnow, and these movements become even more distinct and
        \n\t\t\tfrequent. You might even feel hiccups!
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues with
        \n\t\t\tincreased activity and complex connections forming.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature rapidly. Lungs
        \n\t\t\tare still not ready for breathing outside the womb but
        \n\t\t\tpractice breathing motions. The digestive system absorbs
        \n\t\t\tmore nutrients from amniotic fluid, and taste buds are
        \n\t\t\tdeveloping.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements. Bones continue
        \n\t\t\tto strengthen, and fingernails and toenails become visible
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women by
        \n\t\t\tnow.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week23">
        Your baby\'s ears are getting better at picking up sounds. After
        birth, they may recognize some noises outside the womb that
        they\'re hearing inside now.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a large mango.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 23rd week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a large
        \n\t\t\tmango (around 30cm from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Fetal movement becomes even more frequent
        \n\t\t\tand distinct, and you might even feel hiccups!
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues with more
        \n\t\t\tcomplex activity and connections forming.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature rapidly. Lungs
        \n\t\t\tpractice breathing motions further, the digestive system
        \n\t\t\tabsorbs more nutrients from amniotic fluid, and taste buds
        \n\t\t\tare developing.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements and stronger
        \n\t\t\tkicks. Bones continue to strengthen.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

         Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women by
        \n\t\t\tnow.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week24">
        Your baby cuts a pretty long and lean figure, but chubbier times
        are coming. Their skin is still thin and translucent, but that will
        begin to change soon too.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of an ear of corn.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 24th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of an ear of
        \n\t\t\tcorn (around 31.5cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Fetal movement becomes even more frequent
        \n\t\t\tand distinct, and kicks might feel stronger. You might even
        \n\t\t\tfeel hiccups more often.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly with
        \n\t\t\tcomplex activity and interconnected systems forming.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs practice
        \n\t\t\tbreathing motions further, the digestive system absorbs more
        \n\t\t\tnutrients from amniotic fluid, and taste buds start
        \n\t\t\tfunctioning.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements and stronger
        \n\t\t\tkicks. Bones continue to strengthen, and fingernails and
        \n\t\t\ttoenails are fully formed.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

         Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women by
        \n\t\t\tnow.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week25">
        Your baby\'s wrinkled skin is starting to fill out with baby fat,
        making them look more like a newborn. Their hair is beginning to
        come in, and it has color and texture.\n\n
        Your baby is now the same weight as an average rutabaga.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 25th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of an
        \n\t\t\taverage rutabaga (around 34.6cm long from head to heel).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Fetal movement becomes even more frequent
        \n\t\t\tand distinct, and kicks might feel even stronger. You might be
        \n\t\t\table to identify patterns in your baby\'s activity cycles.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly,
        \n\t\t\twith complex neural connections forming, allowing for more
        \n\t\t\tcoordinated movements and responses to external stimuli.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs practice
        \n\t\t\tbreathing motions further, the digestive system absorbs more
        \n\t\t\tnutrients from amniotic fluid, and taste buds start
        \n\t\t\tfunctioning, even allowing your baby to taste flavors in the
        \n\t\t\tamniotic fluid.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements and stronger
        \n\t\t\tkicks. Bones continue to strengthen, and hair continues to
        \n\t\t\tgrow on the head.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women by
        \n\t\t\tnow.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="week26">
        Your baby is now inhaling and exhaling amniotic fluid, which
        helps develop their lungs. These breathing movements are good
        practice for that first breath of air at birth.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a bunch of scallions.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 26th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a bunch
        \n\t\t\tof scallions. (around 35.8cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Fetal movement becomes even more frequent
        \n\t\t\tand distinct, and kicks might feel even stronger and more
       \n\t\t\tcoordinated. You might be able to identify patterns in your
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s activity cycles and even respond to their movements
        \n\t\t\tby gently touching your belly.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly,
        \n\t\t\twith complex neural connections forming, allowing for more
        \n\t\t\tcoordinated movements, responses to external stimuli, and
        \n\t\t\teven basic learning and memory formation.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs practice
        \n\t\t\tbreathing motions further, the digestive system absorbs more
        \n\t\t\tnutrients from amniotic fluid and starts processing some
        \n\t\t\twaste, and taste buds are functioning, allowing the baby to
        \n\t\t\ttaste flavors in the amniotic fluid
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements and stronger
        \n\t\t\tkicks. Bones continue to strengthen, and hair continues to
        \n\t\t\tgrow on the head.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women by
        \n\t\t\tnow.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="week27">
        This is the last week of your second trimester. Your baby now
        sleeps and wakes on a regular schedule, and their brain is very
        active. Their lungs aren\'t fully formed, but they could function
        outside the womb with medical help.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a head of cauliflower.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 27th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a head of
        \n\t\t\tcauliflower (around 37.1cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Fetal movement becomes even more frequent,
        \n\t\t\tdistinct, and coordinated. You might feel hiccups more often,
        \n\t\t\tand kicks might be quite strong. You can even begin to
        \n\t\t\tinteract with your baby by talking or singing, as they may
        \n\t\t\trespond to your voice and touch.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly,
        \n\t\t\twith complex neural connections forming and allowing for
        \n\t\t\tmore advanced responses to the environment, like tracking
        \n\t\t\tlight and sound.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs practice
        \n\t\t\tbreathing motions further, the digestive system absorbs more
        \n\t\t\tnutrients from amniotic fluid and starts digesting some
        \n\t\t\tbreast milk, and the kidneys begin producing more urine
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles continue to
        \n\t\t\tdevelop, allowing for even more coordinated movements
        \n\t\t\tand stronger kicks. Bones continue to strengthen, and hair
        \n\t\t\tcontinues to grow on the head. Vernix caseosa, a protective
        \n\t\t\twaxy coating, covers the baby\'s skin.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

         Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women by
        \n\t\t\tnow.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="week28">
    Your baby\'s eyesight is developing, which may enable them to
    sense light filtering in from the outside. They can blink, and their
    eyelashes have grown in.\n\n
    Your baby is the size of a large eggplant.\n\n
    Here\'s what happens during the 28th week:\n

       \n\t\t•  Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a large
        \n\t\t\teggplant (around 37.8cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Fetal movement continues to be frequent,
        \n\t\t\tdistinct, and coordinated. You might feel hiccups more often,
        \n\t\t\tand kicks might be even stronger. You can interact with your
        \n\t\t\tbaby by talking or singing, as they may respond to your voice
        \n\t\t\tand touch.
       \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly with
        \n\t\t\tcomplex neural connections forming, allowing for more
        \n\t\t\tadvanced brain activity and responses like grasping and
        \n\t\t\tsucking reflexes.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs practice
        \n\t\t\tbreathing motions further, the digestive system absorbs
       \n\t\t\t nutrients from amniotic fluid and starts digesting breast milk,
        \n\t\t\tand kidneys produce more urine.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for even more coordinated movements and stronger
        \n\t\t\tkicks. Bones continue to strengthen, and hair continues to
        \n\t\t\tgrow on the head. Vernix caseosa, a protective waxy
        \n\t\t\tcoating, covers the baby\'s skin.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Consider getting the Tdap vaccine: This vaccine protects you
        \n\t\t\tand your baby from whooping cough, tetanus, and \n\t\t\tdiphtheria.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>


    <string name="week29">
        Your baby\'s muscles and lungs are busy getting ready to function
        in the outside world, and their head is growing to make room for
        their developing brain.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a butternut squash.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 29th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a
        \n\t\t\tbutternut squash (around 39.9cm from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Fetal movement continues to be frequent,
        \n\t\t\tdistinct, and coordinated. You might feel kicks more intensely
        \n\t\t\tnow, often described as jabs or pokes rather than full-blown
        \n\t\t\tkicks due to space constraints.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly with
        \n\t\t\tcomplex neural connections forming, allowing for more
        \n\t\t\tadvanced brain activity and responses like grasping reflexes,
        \n\t\t\tsucking reflexes, and even opening and closing their eyes.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs practice
        \n\t\t\tbreathing motions more actively, the digestive system
        \n\t\t\tabsorbs nutrients from amniotic fluid and starts practicing
        \n\t\t\tdigesting small amounts of lanugo (fetal hair). The kidneys
        \n\t\t\tproduce more urine, which they release into the amniotic
        \n\t\t\tsac.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for even more coordinated movements and stronger
        \n\t\t\tkicks. Bones continue to strengthen, and hair continues to
        \n\t\t\tgrow on the head. Vernix caseosa, a protective waxy
        \n\t\t\tcoating, covers the baby\'s skin.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Start tracking fetal movement: Most healthcare providers will
        \n\t\t\trecommend starting to track your baby\'s movements around
        \n\t\t\tthis time to ensure their well-being\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="week30">
        Your baby is surrounded by a pint and a half of amniotic fluid,
        although there will be less of it as they grow and claim more
        space inside your uterus.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a large cabbage.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 30th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a large
        \n\t\t\tcabbage (around 39.9cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Fetal movement might seem slightly less frequent
        \n\t\t\tdue to decreasing space, but you should still feel your baby
        \n\t\t\tmoving regularly. Kicks might feel stronger and more focused
        \n\t\t\tas muscles develop.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly with
        \n\t\t\tcomplex neural connections forming, allowing for more
        \n\t\t\tadvanced responses and even rudimentary learning.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs mature
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly, practicing breathing motions more deeply and
        \n\t\t\tregularly. The digestive system starts absorbing some
        \n\t\t\tnutrients from small amounts of amniotic fluid swallowed and
        \n\t\t\tpracticing digesting lanugo (fetal hair). The kidneys produce
        \n\t\t\tmore urine and filter waste products from the blood.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for more coordinated movements and stronger
        \n\t\t\tkicks. Bones continue

        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Start tracking fetal movement seriously: Consistently monitor
        \n\t\t\tyour baby\'s movements and consult your doctor if you notice
        \n\t\t\tany significant changes in frequency or pattern.
        \n\t\t• Consider additional tests: Depending on your specific health
        \n\t\t\tand pregnancy course, your doctor might recommend
        \n\t\t\tadditional tests like a Group B strep test or ultrasound.
        \n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week31">
        Your baby can now turn their head from side to side. A protective
        layer of fat is accumulating under their skin, filling out their arms
        and legs.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a coconut.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 31st week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a coconut
        \n\t\t\t(around 41.1cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Fetal movement might seem even less frequent
        \n\t\t\tdue to space limitations, but you should still feel your baby
        \n\t\t\tmoving regularly. Kicks might feel strong and focused due to
        \n\t\t\tmuscle development.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly,
        \n\t\t\twith complex neural connections forming and allowing for
       \n\t\t\teven more advanced responses and even rudimentary
        \n\t\t\tmemories.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs mature
        \n\t\t\tfurther, practicing deeper and more regular breathing
        \n\t\t\tmotions. The digestive system starts processing some
        \n\t\t\tnutrients
       \n\t\t\tfrom swallowed amniotic fluid and lanugo (fetal hair). The
       \n\t\t\tkidneys produce more urine and filter waste products from
        \n\t\t\tthe blood.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for coordinated movements and stronger kicks.
        \n\t\t\tBones continue to strengthen, and fingernails and toenails
        \n\t\t\tare fully formed.
        \n\t\t• Fat accumulation: Your baby starts accumulating more fat
        \n\t\t\tunder the skin, giving them a plumper appearance.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually identifiable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

         Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

           Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Start tracking fetal movement seriously: Consistently monitor
        \n\t\t\tyour baby\'s movements and consult your doctor if you notice
        \n\t\t\tany significant changes in frequency or pattern.
        \n\t\t• Consider additional tests: Depending on your specific health
        \n\t\t\tand pregnancy course, your doctor might recommend
        \n\t\t\tadditional tests like a Group B strep test or ultrasound.
        \n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="week32">
        You\'re probably gaining about a pound a week now. Half of that
        goes straight to your baby, who will gain one-third to half their
        birth weight in the next seven weeks in preparation for life
        outside the womb.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a large jicama.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 32nd week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a head of
        \n\t\t\ta large jicama (around 42.4cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: You might feel kicks and movements slightly less
        \n\t\t\tfrequently due to limited space, but they should still be
        r\n\t\t\tegular and distinct. Movements might be stronger and more
        \n\t\t\tfocused due to muscle development.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly,
        \n\t\t\twith complex neural connections forming and allowing for
        \n\t\t\teven more advanced responses, reflexes, and even basic
        \n\t\t\tlearning and memory formation.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs mature
        \n\t\t\tfurther, practicing deeper and more regular breathing
        \n\t\t\tmotions. The digestive system continues processing nutrients
        \n\t\t\tfrom amniotic fluid and starts digesting small amounts of
       \n\t\t\t breast milk. The kidneys produce more urine and filter waste
        \n\t\t\tproducts from the blood.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for coordinated movements and strong kicks. Bones
        \n\t\t\tcontinue to strengthen, and hair continues to grow on the
        \n\t\t\thead.
        \n\t\t• Fat accumulation: Your baby continues to accumulate fat
       \n\t\t\t under the skin, giving them a plumper appearance.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually identifiable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

           Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Start tracking fetal movement seriously: Consistently monitor
        \n\t\t\tyour baby\'s movements and consult your doctor if you notice
        \n\t\t\tany significant changes in frequency or pattern.
        \n\t\t• Consider additional tests: Depending on your specific health
        \n\t\t\tand pregnancy course, your doctor might recommend
        \n\t\t\tadditional tests like a Group B strep test or ultrasound.
        \n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week33">
        The bones in your baby\'s skull aren\'t fused yet. That allows them
        to shift as their head squeezes through the birth canal. They
        won\'t fully fuse until adulthood.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a pineapple.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 33rd week:

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a
        \n\t\t\tpineapple (around 43.7cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: You might feel kicks and movements slightly less
        \n\t\t\tfrequently due to limited space, but they should still be
        \n\t\t\tregular and distinct. Movements might feel stronger and
        \n\t\t\tmore focused due to muscle development.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development remains rapid, with
        \n\t\t\teven more complex neural connections forming and allowing
        \n\t\t\tfor advanced responses, reflexes, and even the potential to
        \n\t\t\tdream.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs mature
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly, practicing deeper and more regular breathing
        \n\t\t\tmotions. The digestive system continues processing nutrients
        \n\t\t\tfrom amniotic fluid and starts digesting small amounts of
        \n\t\t\tbreast milk. The kidneys produce more urine and filter waste
        \n\t\t\tproducts from the blood.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for coordinated movements and strong kicks. Bones
        \n\t\t\tcontinue to strengthen, and hair continues to grow on the
        \n\t\t\thead.
        \n\t\t• Fat accumulation: Your baby continues to accumulate fat
        \n\t\t\tunder the skin, giving them a plumper appearance.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually identifiable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• Increased vaginal discharge: You might experience increased
        \n\t\t\tclear or white discharge, which is normal as long as it is not
        \n\t\t\todorous or green.
        \n\t\t• Swelling in hands and feet: Mild swelling might occur due to
        \n\t\t\tincreased fluid retention.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n


           Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Start tracking fetal movement seriously: Consistently monitor
        \n\t\t\tyour baby\'s movements and consult your doctor if you notice
        \n\t\t\tany significant changes in frequency or pattern.
        \n\t\t• Consider additional tests: Depending on your specific health
        \n\t\t\tand pregnancy course, your doctor might recommend
        \n\t\t\tadditional tests like a Group B strep test or ultrasound.
        \n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
            </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="week34">
        Your baby\'s central nervous system is maturing, as are their lungs.
        Babies born between 34 and 37 weeks who have no other health
        problems usually do well in the long run.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a cantaloupe.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 34th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a
        \n\t\t\tpineapple (around 45cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: You might feel kicks and movements slightly less
        \n\t\t\tfrequently due to limited space, but they should still be
        \n\t\t\tregular and distinct. Movements might feel stronger and
        \n\t\t\tmore focused due to muscle development.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development remains rapid, with
        \n\t\t\teven more complex neural connections forming and allowing
        \n\t\t\tfor advanced responses, reflexes, and even the potential to
        \n\t\t\tdream.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature. Lungs mature
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly, practicing deeper and more regular breathing
        \n\t\t\tmotions. The digestive system continues processing nutrients
        \n\t\t\tfrom amniotic fluid and starts digesting small amounts of
        \n\t\t\tbreast milk. The kidneys produce more urine and filter waste
        \n\t\t\tproducts from the blood.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles develop further,
        \n\t\t\tallowing for coordinated movements and strong kicks. Bones
        \n\t\t\tcontinue to strengthen, and hair continues to grow on the
        \n\t\t\thead.
        \n\t\t• Fat accumulation: Your baby continues to accumulate fat
        \n\t\t\tunder the skin, giving them a plumper appearance.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually identifiable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Many women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• Increased vaginal discharge: You might experience increased
        \n\t\t\tclear or white discharge, which is normal as long as it is not
        \n\t\t\todorous or green.
        \n\t\t• Swelling in hands and feet: Mild swelling might occur due to
        \n\t\t\tincreased fluid retention.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n


           Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Start tracking fetal movement seriously: Consistently monitor
        \n\t\t\tyour baby\'s movements and consult your doctor if you notice
        \n\t\t\tany significant changes in frequency or pattern.
        \n\t\t• Consider additional tests: Depending on your specific health
        \n\t\t\tand pregnancy course, your doctor might recommend
        \n\t\t\tadditional tests like a Group B strep test or ultrasound.
        \n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>


    <string name="week35">
        It\'s getting snug inside your womb – but you should still feel your
        baby moving as much as ever. Your baby\'s kidneys are fully
        developed, and their liver can process some waste products.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a honeydew melon.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 35th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby now measures around 46.2 cm long
        \n\t\t\tfrom head to toe, roughly the size of a honeydew melon.
        \n\t\t• Movement: While space is becoming more limited, you should
        \n\t\t\tstill feel regular fetal movements. They might feel different,
        \n\t\t\twith more rolls and wiggles instead of strong kicks.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly,
        \n\t\t\twith complex neural connections forming and allowing for
        \n\t\t\teven more advanced responses, reflexes, and even
        \n\t\t\trudimentary learning and memory formation.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature and prepare for
        \n\t\t\tfunctioning after birth. Lungs mature significantly, practicing
        \n\t\t\tdeeper and more regular breathing motions. The digestive
        \n\t\t\tsystem continues practicing digestion of amniotic fluid and
       \n\t\t\tsmall amounts of breast milk. The kidneys produce more
        \n\t\t\turine and filter waste products from the blood.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles continue to
        \n\t\t\tdevelop, allowing for coordinated movements. Bones
        \n\t\t\tcontinue to strengthen, and hair, fingernails, and toenails are
        \n\t\t\tfully formed.
        \n\t\t• Fat accumulation: Your baby continues to accumulate fat
        \n\t\t\tunder the skin, giving them a plumper, rounder appearance.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually identifiable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Some women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• Increased vaginal discharge: You might experience increased
        \n\t\t\tclear or white discharge, which is normal as long as it is not
        \n\t\t\todorous or green.
        \n\t\t• Swelling in hands and feet: Mild swelling might occur due to
        \n\t\t\tincreased fluid retention.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health Interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Track fetal movement consistently: Monitor your baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tmovements and consult your doctor if you notice any
        \n\t\t\tsignificant changes in frequency or pattern.
        \n\t\t• Consider additional tests: Depending on your specific health
        \n\t\t\tand pregnancy course, your doctor might recommend
        \n\t\t\tadditional tests like a Group B strep test or a non-stress test.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week36">
        Your baby is gaining about an ounce a day. They\'re also losing
        most of their lanugo hair that covered their body, along with the
        vernix caseosa, a waxy substance that was protecting their skin
        until now.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a head of romaine lettuce.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 36th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a head of
        \n\t\t\tromaine lettuce (around 47.4 cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: Movement: Fetal movement may seem slightly
        \n\t\t\tless frequent due to decreasing space, but you should still
        \n\t\t\tfeel your baby moving regularly. Kicks might feel stronger
        \n\t\t\tand more focused as muscles develop.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues rapidly,
        \n\t\t\twith complex neural connections forming and allowing for
        \n\t\t\teven more advanced responses, reflexes, and even
        \n\t\t\trudimentary learning and memory formation.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs continue to mature and prepare for
        \n\t\t\tfunctioning after birth. Lungs mature significantly, practicing
        \n\t\t\tdeeper and more regular breathing motions. The digestive
        \n\t\t\tsystem continues practicing digestion of amniotic fluid and
       \n\t\t\tsmall amounts of breast milk. The kidneys produce more
        \n\t\t\turine and filter waste products from the blood.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles continue to
        \n\t\t\tdevelop, allowing for coordinated movements. Bones
        \n\t\t\tcontinue to strengthen, and hair, fingernails, and toenails are
        \n\t\t\tfully formed.
        \n\t\t• Fat accumulation: Your baby continues to accumulate fat
        \n\t\t\tunder the skin, giving them a plumper, rounder appearance.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually identifiable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Some women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• Increased vaginal discharge: You might experience increased
        \n\t\t\tclear or white discharge, which is normal as long as it is not
        \n\t\t\todorous or green.
        \n\t\t• Swelling in hands and feet: Mild swelling might occur due to
        \n\t\t\tincreased fluid retention.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Start tracking fetal movement seriously: Consistently monitor
        \n\t\t\tyour baby\'s movements and consult your doctor if you notice
        \n\t\t\tany significant changes in frequency or pattern.
        \n\t\t• Consider additional tests: Depending on your specific health
        \n\t\t\tand pregnancy course, your doctor might recommend
        \n\t\t\tadditional tests like a Group B strep test or ultrasound.
        \n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week37">
        Your due date is very close, and though your baby looks like a
        newborn, they\'re not considered full-term until 39 weeks. Over
        the next two weeks, their lungs and brain will continue to mature.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a bunch of Swiss chard.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 37th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a bunch
        \n\t\t\tof Swiss chard (around 48.6 cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: You might still feel regular fetal movements, but
        \n\t\t\tthey might be less frequent due to limited space. Kicks might
        \n\t\t\tfeel stronger and more focused due to muscle development.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues steadily,
        \n\t\t\twith complex neural connections forming and allowing for
        \n\t\t\teven more advanced responses and even rudimentary
        \n\t\t\tlearning and memory formation.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs are fully developed and mature,
        \n\t\t\tready to function after birth. The lungs practice deeper and
        \n\t\t\tmore regular breathing motions in preparation for their first
        \n\t\t\tbreaths. The digestive system continues practicing digestion
        \n\t\t\tof amniotic fluid and small amounts of breast milk. The
        \n\t\t\tkidneys produce more urine and filter waste products from
        \n\t\t\tthe blood.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles are well
        \n\t\t\tdeveloped, allowing for strong and coordinated movements.
        \n\t\t\tBones continue to strengthen, and hair, fingernails, and
        \n\t\t\ttoenails are fully formed.
        \n\t\t• Fat accumulation: Your baby continues to accumulate fat
        \n\t\t\tunder the skin, giving them a plumper, rounder appearance.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully developed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually identifiable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.

         Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Some women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• Increased vaginal discharge: You might experience increased
        \n\t\t\tclear or white discharge, which is normal as long as it is not
        \n\t\t\todorous or green.
        \n\t\t• Swelling in hands and feet: Mild swelling might occur due to
        \n\t\t\tincreased fluid retention.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Start tracking fetal movement seriously: Consistently monitor
        \n\t\t\tyour baby\'s movements and consult your doctor if you notice
        \n\t\t\tany significant changes in frequency or pattern.
        \n\t\t• Consider additional tests: Depending on your specific health
        \n\t\t\tand pregnancy course, your doctor might recommend
        \n\t\t\tadditional tests like a Group B strep test or ultrasound.
        \n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week38">
        Are you curious about your baby\'s eye color? Their irises aren\'t
        fully pigmented at birth, so their eyes could change color up until
        they\'re about a year old.
        Your baby is the size of a leek.
        Here\'s what happens during the 38th week:\n\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a leek
        \n\t\t\t(around 49.8 cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: You might feel fetal movements slightly less
        \n\t\t\tfrequently due to limited space, but they should still be
        \n\t\t\tregular and distinct. Movements might feel stronger and
        \n\t\t\tmorefocused due to muscle development.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues steadily,
        \n\t\t\twith more complex neural connections forming and allowing
        \n\t\t\tfor advanced responses, reflexes, and even rudimentary
        \n\t\t\tlearning and memory formation.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs are fully developed and mature,
        \n\t\t\tready to function after birth. The lungs are nearly ready for
        \n\t\t\ttheir first breaths outside the womb. The digestive system
        \n\t\t\tcontinues practicing digestion of amniotic fluid and small
        \n\t\t\tamounts of breast milk. The kidneys produce more urine and
        \n\t\t\tfilter waste products from the blood.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles are well
        \n\t\t\tdeveloped, allowing for strong and coordinated movements.
        \n\t\t\tBones continue to strengthen, and hair, fingernails, and
        \n\t\t\ttoenails are fully formed.
        \n\t\t• Fat accumulation: Your baby continues to accumulate fat
        \n\t\t\tunder the skin, giving them a plumper, rounder appearance.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully developed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually identifiable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.

         Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Some women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more prominent,
        \n\t\t\tand some women might experience skin changes like a
        \n\t\t\t"\pregnancy glow"\or linea nigra.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• Increased vaginal discharge: You might experience increased
        \n\t\t\tclear or white discharge, which is normal as long as it is not
        \n\t\t\todorous or green.
        \n\t\t• Swelling in hands and feet: Mild swelling might occur due to
        \n\t\t\tincreased fluid retention.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor if you have any
        \n\t\t\tconcerns or risk factors and whether prenatal
        \n\t\t\tscreening tests like an anomaly scan are right for you.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Start tracking fetal movement seriously: Consistently monitor
        \n\t\t\tyour baby\'s movements and consult your doctor if you notice
        \n\t\t\tany significant changes in frequency or pattern.
        \n\t\t• Consider additional tests: Depending on your specific health
        \n\t\t\tand pregnancy course, your doctor might recommend
        \n\t\t\tadditional tests like a Group B strep test or ultrasound.
        \n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week39">
        Your baby\'s physical development is complete, but they\'re still
        busy putting on fat and growing bigger.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a mini watermelon.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 39th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby reaches about the size of a mini
        \n\t\t\twatermelon (around 50.7 cm long from head to toe).
        \n\t\t• Movement: You might feel fetal movements slightly less
        \n\t\t\tfrequently due to limited space, but they should still be
        \n\t\t\tregular and distinct. Movements might feel different with
        \n\t\t\tmore rolls and wiggles instead of strong kicks due to space
        \n\t\t\tconstraints.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues steadily,
        \n\t\t\twith complex neural connections forming and allowing for
        \n\t\t\teven more advanced responses, reflexes, and even
        \n\t\t\trudimentary learning and memory formation.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs are fully developed and mature,
        \n\t\t\tready to function independently after birth. The lungs are
        \n\t\t\tnearly ready for their first breaths, and the digestive system
        \n\t\t\tcontinues practicing digestion of amniotic fluid and small
        \n\t\t\tamounts of breast milk.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Some women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger as their bodies
        \n\t\t\tadjust to pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Reduced or absent nausea: Morning sickness should be
        \n\t\t\tsignificantly improved or gone completely for most women
        \n\t\t\tby now.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes even more
        \n\t\t\tprominent, and skin changes like a \"pregnancy glow\" or linea
        \n\t\t\tnigra might become more noticeable. Stretch marks may
        \n\t\t\tbecome more noticeable.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but less often
        \n\t\t\tthan before.
       \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: As your uterus grows and your center of gravity
        \n\t\t\tshifts, backaches can become more frequent.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still happen, but
        \n\t\t\thopefully less intense and frequent.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These are painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions that you might feel occasionally throughout the
        \n\t\t\tsecond and third trimesters. They become more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcloser to term.
        \n\t\t• Nesting instinct: You might feel a sudden urge to clean,
        \n\t\t\torganize, and prepare for the baby\'s arrival.
        \n\t\t• Loss of mucus plug: You might lose the mucus plug that seals
        \n\t\t\tthe cervix, which can be a sign that labor is approaching.
        \n\t\t\tHowever, it doesn\'t necessarily mean immediate birth
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, every pregnancy is unique, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might not experience noticeable symptoms.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for continued healthy development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\tmoderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\thydrated.
        \n\t\t• Manage common discomforts: Discuss with your doctor ways
        \n\t\t\tto manage heartburn, indigestion, backaches, shortness of
        \n\t\t\tbreath, Braxton Hicks contractions, or other discomforts you
        \n\t\t\tmight experience.
        \n\t\t• Start tracking fetal movement seriously: Consistently monitor
        \n\t\t\tyour baby\'s movements and consult your doctor if you notice
        \n\t\t\tany significant changes in frequency or pattern.
        \n\t\t• Consider additional tests: Depending on your specific health
        \n\t\t\tand pregnancy course, your doctor might recommend
        \n\t\t\tadditional tests like a non-stress test or biophysical profile.\n\n


         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a gradual increase in
        \n\t\t\tweight as your body nourishes the growing baby
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for the second trimester.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You\'ll have a more defined baby bump, and
        \n\t\t\tsome women might notice changes in skin, hair, or nails.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week40">
        If you\'re past your due date, you may not be as late as you think,
        especially if you calculated it solely based on the day of your last
        period. Sometimes women ovulate later than expected.\n\n
        Your provider will continuously assess your pregnancy to make
        sure you can safely continue your pregnancy.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a small pumpkin.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 40th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby is fully developed and ready for
        \n\t\t\tbirth, reaching an average size of 51 cm long and weighing
        \n\t\t\taround 3.4 kg. However, they can continue to grow slightly in
        \n\t\t\tthese final days.
        \n\t\t• Movement: You might feel fetal movements even less
        \n\t\t\tfrequently due to limited space, but they should still be
        \n\t\t\tregular and distinct. Movements might feel different with
        \n\t\t\tmore rolls and wiggles rather than strong kicks.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues, but at a
        \n\t\t\tslower pace compared to earlier weeks. The brain is fully
        \n\t\t\tequipped for life outside the womb.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs are fully mature and prepared to
        \n\t\t\tfunction independently after birth. The lungs are ready for
        \n\t\t\ttheir first breaths, the digestive system is ready to start
        \n\t\t\tprocessing breast milk, and the kidneys are filtering waste
        \n\t\t\teffectively.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles are well
        \n\t\t\tdeveloped, allowing for coordinated movements. Bones are
        \n\t\t\t fully formed and strong.
        \n\t\t• Fat accumulation: Fat accumulation slows down significantly,
        \n\t\t\tand your baby focuses on storing energy reserves for after
        \n\t\t\tbirth. They have a plumper, rounder appearance due to
        \n\t\t\taccumulated fat.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully developed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually identifiable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Some women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger, while others might
        \n\t\t\tfeel their energy levels stabilize.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump might feel lower in your
        \n\t\t\tpelvis as the baby engages, preparing for birth. Skin
        \n\t\t\tchanges like a \"pregnancy glow\"or linea nigra might fade
        \n\t\t\tgradually.
        Stretch marks may become more noticeable.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but might reduce
        \n\t\t\tif the baby engages in your pelvis.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: Backaches can continue, especially as your
        \n\t\t\tposture changes with the baby engaged.
        \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions become more frequent and noticeable as your
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for labor. They might even feel slightly
        \n\t\t\tuncomfortable at times.
        \n\t\t• Increased vaginal discharge: You might experience
        \n\t\t\tincreased clear or white discharge, which is normal as long
        \n\t\t\tas it is not odorous or green.
        \n\t\t• Loss of mucus plug: You might lose the mucus plug that seals
        \n\t\t\tthe cervix, which can be a sign that labor is approaching.
        \n\t\t\tHowever, it doesn\'t necessarily mean immediate birth.
        \n\t\t• Water breaking: Your water breaking, or rupture of
        \n\t\t\tmembranes, signifies the start of labor. This can be a slow
        \n\t\t\ttrickle or a sudden gush of fluid.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Some women might not experience any
        \n\t\t\tnoticeable signs of labor even at 40 weeks.\n\n

        Health Interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamins: Maintaining your prenatal
        \n\t\t\tvitamin intake is crucial for your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tdevelopment, even at this late stage.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\tprogress. They might recommend inducing labor if you reach
        \n\t\t\t41 weeks without signs of labor starting spontaneously.
        \n\t\t• Stay hydrated: Drinking plenty of water is important for both
        \n\t\t\tyou and your baby.
        \n\t\t• Rest and relaxation: Getting enough sleep and rest is crucial
        \n\t\t\tfor your energy levels and preparing for labor.
        \n\t\t• Listen to your body: Pay attention to any changes in your
        \n\t\t\tbody or baby\'s movement and inform your doctor
        \n\t\t\timmediately if you have any concerns.\n\n

        Expectations for Your Body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: Weight gain usually slows down or
        \n\t\t\tplateaus in the final weeks.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for labor.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump might feel lower in your
        \n\t\t\tpelvis, and your breasts might start producing colostrum, a
        \n\t\t\tpre-milk substance.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips. Consider
        \n\t\t\tusing pregnancy pillows or adjusting your sleep positions for
        \n\t\t\tbetter comfort.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="week41">
        Your baby is now considered late-term. Going more than two
        weeks past your due date can put you and your baby at risk for
        complications, so your provider will probably talk to you about
        inducing labor. They may perform a non-stress test (NST) to
        monitor your baby\'s fetal heart rate and your contractions to
        make sure your baby isn\'t in any distress.\n\n

        Here\'s what happens during the 41st week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal Growth: Your baby is considered \"post-term\"
        or \"late\n\t\t\tterm\" at this point. While still healthy, they might continue to
        \n\t\t\tgrow slightly, exceeding average size and weight.
        \n\t\t• Movement: You might feel fetal movements even less
        \n\t\t\tfrequently due to limited space, but they should still be
        \n\t\t\tregular and distinct. Pay close attention to any changes in
        \n\t\t\tmovement and consult your doctor if you notice a significant
       \n\t\t\tdecrease.
        \n\t\t• Brain development: Brain development continues, but at a
        \n\t\t\tslower pace than earlier weeks. The brain is fully equipped
        \n\t\t\tfor life outside the womb
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Organs are fully mature and prepared to
        \n\t\t\tfunction independently after birth. The lungs are ready for
        \n\t\t\ttheir first breaths, the digestive system is ready to start
        \n\t\t\tprocessing breast milk, and the kidneys are filtering waste
        \n\t\t\teffectively.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and skeletal development: Muscles are well
        \n\t\t\tdeveloped, allowing for coordinated movements. Bones are
        \n\t\t\t fully formed and strong.
        \n\t\t• Fat accumulation: Fat accumulation slows down significantly,
        \n\t\t\tand your baby focuses on storing energy reserves for after
        \n\t\t\tbirth. They have a plumper, rounder appearance due to
        \n\t\t\taccumulated fat.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully developed, and the
        \n\t\t\tbaby\'s sex is usually identifiable through ultrasound, if
        \n\t\t\tdesired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Increased energy and appetite: Some women experience
        \n\t\t\tcontinued increased energy and hunger, while others might
        \n\t\t\tfeel their energy levels stabilize.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump might feel lower in your
        \n\t\t\tpelvis as the baby engages, preparing for birth. Skin
        \n\t\t\tchanges like a \"pregnancy glow\"or linea nigra might fade
        \n\t\t\tgradually.
        Stretch marks may become more noticeable.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This might still occur due to increased
        \n\t\t\tblood volume and pressure on the bladder, but might reduce
        \n\t\t\tif the baby engages in your pelvis.
        \n\t\t• Backaches: Backaches can continue, especially as your
        \n\t\t\tposture changes with the baby engaged.
        \n\t\t• Round ligament pain: You might experience occasional sharp
        \n\t\t\tpains on your sides due to the expanding uterus stretching
        \n\t\t\tligaments.
        \n\t\t• Heartburn and indigestion: As your growing uterus pushes on
        \n\t\t\tyour stomach, you might experience heartburn and
        \n\t\t\tindigestion more frequently.
        \n\t\t• Shortness of breath: As your uterus expands, it can push up
        \n\t\t\ton your diaphragm, making it harder to take deep breaths.
        \n\t\t• Braxton Hicks contractions: These painless practice
        \n\t\t\tcontractions become more frequent and noticeable as your
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for labor. They might even feel slightly
        \n\t\t\tuncomfortable at times.
        \n\t\t• Increased vaginal discharge: You might experience
        \n\t\t\tincreased clear or white discharge, which is normal as long
        \n\t\t\tas it is not odorous or green.
        \n\t\t• Loss of mucus plug: You might lose the mucus plug that seals
        \n\t\t\tthe cervix, which can be a sign that labor is approaching.
        \n\t\t\tHowever, it doesn\'t necessarily mean immediate birth.
        \n\t\t• Water breaking: Your water breaking, or rupture of
        \n\t\t\tmembranes, signifies the start of labor. This can be a slow
        \n\t\t\ttrickle or a sudden gush of fluid.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Some women might not experience any
        \n\t\t\tnoticeable signs of labor even at 40 weeks.\n\n

        Health Interventions:
        \n\t\t• Close monitoring: Your doctor will schedule more frequent
        \n\t\t\tcheck-ups to monitor your baby\'s health and well-being
        \n\t\t\tthrough ultrasounds and non-stress tests.
        \n\t\t• Induction of labor: Depending on your specific situation and
        \n\t\t\tyour doctor\'s recommendation, inducing labor might be
        \n\t\t\tconsidered after discussing the risks and benefits.
        \n\t\t• Stay hydrated: Drinking plenty of water is important for both
        \n\t\t\tyou and your baby.
        \n\t\t• Rest and relaxation: Getting enough sleep and rest is crucial
        \n\t\t\tfor your energy levels and preparing for labor.
        \n\t\t• Listen to your body: Pay close attention to any changes in
        \n\t\t\tyour body or baby\'s movement and inform your doctor
        \n\t\t\timmediately if you have any concerns.\n\n

        Expectations for Your Body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: Weight gain usually slows down or
        \n\t\t\tplateaus in the final weeks.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Not relevant for tracking pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tanymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thinner and clearer as the
        \n\t\t\tbody prepares for labor.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump might feel lower in your
        \n\t\t\tpelvis, and your breasts might start producing colostrum, a
        \n\t\t\tpre-milk substance.
        \n\t\t• Sleep: You might find it challenging to sleep comfortably due
        \n\t\t\tto the growing belly and frequent bathroom trips. Consider
        \n\t\t\tusing pregnancy pillows or adjusting your sleep positions for
        \n\t\t\tbetter comfort.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\tabout your pregnancy health and well-being
    </string>


    <string name="agreement_title">GENERAL TERMS</string>
    <string name="agreement_1_1">
        • The mobile application "SafeNest" was made by and is the property of Lou Sophia M. Laud, Noela Mae E. Malong, Myrh Leslie M. Radam, Kristine B. Servania, and Regine A. Tacuban. The current user agreement regulates your usage of the application.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_1_2">
        • The "SafeNest" mobile application, contingent upon the wholehearted adherence to the agreement, is an informative application, developed for mobile devices operating the android operating systems. The right to the intellectual property of the application is owned by the researchers.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_1_3">
        • By installing and using the application, you agree to the conditions of our current agreement. If you do not agree with any of the clauses in our current agreement, you do not have the right to use the application.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_1_4">
        • The copyright holder has the right to introduce any changes to the current agreement without prior notice. New revisions to the agreement enter into force from the moment they appear on the application. You commit to monitoring changes to the agreement yourself. Continuing to use the application after changes are made to the current agreement will indicate your agreement with these changes.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_1_5">
        • Appeals, suggestions and complaints by natural and legal persons to the copyright holder linked to the content and function of the application, the violation of rights and interests of third parties, can be sent to the e-mail address safenestdigitalcompanion@gmail.com.
    </string>

    <string name="agreement_2_title">TERMS OF USE</string>
    <string name="agreement_2_1">
        • The user is obliged to duly follow the conditions of our current agreement.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_2">
        • The user commits to not use the application for any purpose other than for the purpose of non-commercial personal use.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_4">
       • The user is prohibited from performing the activities listed below, and they are obliged not to perform them.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_4_1">
        ○ Studying and learning the technology, decompilation, disassembling, modifying, as well as attempting to obtain the application\'s source code by any means.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_4_2">
        ○ Using our trademark or logo, or the company content without our explicit written permission.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_4_3">
        ○ Modifying the application by making changes to or forging the instructions and data when the application is operating, as well as any use or distribution of the application and making it available to the general public for commercial and non-commercial purposes.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_4_4">
        ○ Copying and modifying the application, creating derivative goods based on it.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_4_5">
        ○ Distributing or transferring to a third party (including to rent or on loan).
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_4_6">
        ○ Distributing false or derogatory claims to mislead or deceive, as well as to cause harm or damage to the researchers and its affiliates.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_4_7">
        ○ Performing actions which will or could cause harm or damage to the researchers.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_4_8">
        ○ Impersonating another person, as well as falsely claiming to be linked to the researchers or our affiliates.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_4_9">
        ○ Inducing other individuals to perform the activities listed or enabling them to perform any of the activities listed.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_5">
        • The user acknowledges that the application is solely intended for educational purposes and may not be used as a replacement for medical recommendations, diagnosis or treatment.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_2_6">
        • The user understands that the application does not guarantee and does not claim the accuracy of the information provided.
    </string>

    <string name="agreement_3_title">RIGHTS AND OBLIGATIONS OF THE RESEARCHERS</string>
    <string name="agreement_3_1">
        • The researchers have the right to send information about the functionality of the application to the user by any means - including by placing informative and other messages within the application.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_3_2">
        • The researchers have the right to transfer the rights and obligations of the current agreement to third parties for the purpose of fulfilling the current agreement without further consent of the user.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_3_3">
        • The copyright holder has the right, when necessary, at the copyright holder\'s discretion to block or limit access to the application to all users or to an individual user in particular without notice in advance, including in the event the user breaks the conditions of the agreement.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_3_4">
       • The researchers have the right to collect and use technical data and information linked to it, as well as information on the software of the user\'s device, system and applications. The researchers have the right to use this information (on the condition that it is impossible to identify the identity of the user) for the purpose of improving its products or to offer the user its services and technologies.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_3_6">
        • The researchers have the right to modify and delete any content in the application at its discretion.
    </string>

    <string name="agreement_4_title">EXCLUSIVE RIGHTS TO THE APPLICATION</string>
    <string name="agreement_4_1">
        • All materials and services provided available in the application, including trademark, design elements, text, graphics and images, sounds, illustrations and other materials, are subjects of exclusive rights and/or personal non-property rights of the copyright holders.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_4_2">
        • Using the contents of the application is only possible within the functional confines offered by the application. The contents of the application cannot be used in any other way without the prior written consent of the copyright holder.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_4_3">
        • The use of the contents of the application by the user for personal, non-commercial use is allowed under the condition that all signs of copyright protection, related rights, trademarks, and other notices of authorship, and name of authorship are preserved.
    </string>

    <string name="agreement_5_title">GUARANTEES AND RESPONSIBILITIES OF THE PARTIES</string>
    <string name="agreement_5_1">
        • Third parties may be involved to implement the current agreement. The user confirms that the third parties have the same rights as the owner of the rights to the application.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_5_2">
        • The user guarantees that he/she will not take any type of action intended to cause damage to the rights holder of the application, the copyright holder and other parties.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_5_3">
        • If the user does not prove otherwise, any action performed by using their mobile device is considered to have been performed by the corresponding user.
    </string>

    <string name="agreement_6_title">OTHER PROVISIONS</string>
    <string name="agreement_6_1">
        • Our current agreement enters into force for the user from the moment the application is installed on their mobile device. The current agreement is valid indefinitely.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_6_2">
        • The current agreement may be changed and/or added to by the copyright holders at any time during the duration of the validity of the agreement. All changes and/or additions by the copyright holders are placed in the corresponding section of the application and enter into force the day of their placement. The user agrees to timely and independently familiarize themselves with all the changes and/or additions. If there are any objections, the user has the right to make and send notice within 3 calendar days from the moment of the placement of changes and/or additions to the agreement. In this case, the agreement will be considered to be terminated by the parties from the date the copyright holder receives such notice from the user.
    </string>
    <string name="agreement_6_3">
        • If any of the clauses of the current agreement are recognized as invalid, this will not bear any influence or effect on the validity or application of the remaining clauses of the current agreement.
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

        <string name="weeks_1_4_message">Congratulations on your first trimester of pregnancy! No pregnancy symptoms yet, as implantation is just happening or hasn\'t occurred.</string>
        <string name="weeks_5_8_message">Congratulations on reaching this milestone! You might be experiencing common symptoms like implantation bleeding (light spotting), fatigue, breast tenderness, and the onset of nausea and vomiting (morning sickness).</string>
        <string name="weeks_9_12_message">Well done on progressing through the first trimester! At this stage, morning sickness may peak, but you may also notice a reduction in fatigue and breast tenderness. Additionally, you might experience increased urination, food cravings or aversions, and mood swings.</string>
        <string name="weeks_13_16_message">Congratulations on entering your second trimester! You\'ve made it through the initial challenges! Morning sickness usually subsides, and you might feel more energetic. Your belly starts to show, and common symptoms include heartburn, constipation, and backaches.</string>
        <string name="weeks_17_20_message">You\'re halfway there! Congratulations on feeling the baby move for the first time (quickening). Your belly is growing more prominent, and you might notice stretch marks, varicose veins, and hemorrhoids.</string>
        <string name="weeks_21_26_message">You\'re progressing well! Baby movement becomes more frequent and noticeable. You might have difficulty sleeping due to discomfort and increased bathroom visits.</string>
        <string name="weeks_27_30_message">Congratulations on entering your third trimester! You\'re in the final stretch! Braxton Hicks contractions might become more frequent. You might experience swelling in your hands and feet, shortness of breath, and forgetfulness.</string>
        <string name="weeks_31_34_message">Almost there! Baby movement might change as they run out of space. You might experience pelvic pressure, fatigue, and difficulty finding a comfortable sleeping position.</string>
        <string name="weeks_35_42_message">Congratulations on approaching the finish line! Braxton Hicks contractions continue, and you might experience cervical effacement and dilation as your body prepares for labor. Look out for signs like increased vaginal discharge, losing your mucus plug, and water breaking. Best wishes for the remainder of your pregnancy journey!</string>
        <string name="default_pregnancy_message">Your pregnancy journey is progressing!</string>

</resources>